1. creds = findTestData("Data Files/Login_Credentials_Random")
5. assert creds != null : "Test data not found: Data Files/Login_Credentials_Random"
9. logInfo("[DEBUG] class=" + getClass().getName())
13. logInfo("[DEBUG] type=" + creds.getType())
17. logInfo("[DEBUG] sourceUrl=" + creds.getSourceUrl())
21. logInfo("[DEBUG] rowCount=" + creds.getRowNumbers())
25. rowCount = creds.getRowNumbers()
29. assert rowCount > 0 : "No rows found in Data Files/Login_Credentials_Random"
33. pickedRow = 1 + Random().nextInt(rowCount)
37. username = creds.getValue("username", pickedRow)
41. password = creds.getValue("password", pickedRow)
45. openBrowser("")
49. maximizeWindow()
53. navigateToUrl(G_SiteURL)
57. waitForElementVisible(byCss("#btn-make-appointment"), G_Timeout)
1. to = new com.kms.katalon.core.testobject.TestObject((css= + css))
5. to.addProperty("css", EQUALS, css)
9. return to
61. click(byCss("#btn-make-appointment"))
1. to = new com.kms.katalon.core.testobject.TestObject((css= + css))
5. to.addProperty("css", EQUALS, css)
9. return to
65. waitForElementVisible(byCss("#login"), G_Timeout)
1. to = new com.kms.katalon.core.testobject.TestObject((css= + css))
5. to.addProperty("css", EQUALS, css)
9. return to
69. verifyElementPresent(byCss("#login"), G_Timeout)
1. to = new com.kms.katalon.core.testobject.TestObject((css= + css))
5. to.addProperty("css", EQUALS, css)
9. return to
73. waitForElementVisible(byCss("#txt-username"), G_Timeout)
1. to = new com.kms.katalon.core.testobject.TestObject((css= + css))
5. to.addProperty("css", EQUALS, css)
9. return to
77. setText(byCss("#txt-username"), username)
1. to = new com.kms.katalon.core.testobject.TestObject((css= + css))
5. to.addProperty("css", EQUALS, css)
9. return to
81. waitForElementVisible(byCss("#txt-password"), G_Timeout)
1. to = new com.kms.katalon.core.testobject.TestObject((css= + css))
5. to.addProperty("css", EQUALS, css)